

## **Profile**

Medical Imaging Master Student with a track record of leadership and work, knowledgeable about machine learning algorithms, implementations, and research methodologies, committed to studying and exploring up-to-date research trends, and dedicated to helping others to reach their dreams.

#### Education

#### MSc in Medical Imaging, Coordinated by the University of Girona, Spain

SEPTEMBER 2021 — MAY 2023

• Erasmus Mundus Joint Masters Scholarship Holder.

#### BSc in Computer Engineering, Cairo University, Egypt

SEPTEMBER 2017 — MAY 2021

• GPA 3.8 (Salutatorian)

# American Diploma, Egyptian American International School (EAIS), Cairo, Egypt

SEPTEMBER 2013 — MAY 2016

• GPA 3.98 (Valedictorian)

## **Experience**

## Industrial Mentorship, Dell Technologies, Cairo, Egypt

MARCH 2021 — JULY 2021

- BSc Thesis: Scalable Video Surveillance System for Contact Tracing.
- Envision the Future Competition: Top 20 Projects in the MENA Region

#### Research Intern, University of Bradford, Bradford, UK

SEPTEMBER 2020 — DECEMBER 2020

• HEIF Research Project in COVID-19 Data.

## Research Trainee, AIIT, Tokyo, Japan

JULY 2019 — AUGUST 2019

• Funded by the Ministry of Higher Education in Egypt.

## **Major Projects**

#### Pedestrian Detection (PERSOLO), Cairo, Egypt

MARCH 2021 — JULY 2021

• 3<sup>nd</sup> on MOT20 Detection Benchmark Statistics.

## Tracking Multiple People Over a Network of Cameras, Cairo, Egypt

MARCH 2021 — JULY 2021

#### Covid-19 & Big Data Analytics, Bradford, UK

SEPTEMBER 2020 — DECEMBER 2020

Developed deep learning algorithms for time series forecasting.

#### **Details**

Le Creusot, France +330769829447 marwankefah@gmail.com

#### Links

<u>Linkedin</u> <u>Github</u>

#### **Hobbies**

Travelling (18 countries), Hiking Camping, Dancing, culture exchange.

#### Skills/Interests

Expertise in Python / R
Projects with C, C++, C#, Java.

**Computer Vision** 

Machine Learning

**Research Methodologies** 

Software Development

**Image Processing** 

**Probabilistic Robotics** 

Leadership Skills & Teamwork

**Time Series Forecasting** 

**Natural Language Processing** 

JavaScript

MATLAB

Linux/Unix

Verilog/VHDL

NI instruments, Quartus, ModelSim, Multisim, LabView

HTML/CSS, Mongo DB, SQL, MySQL

#### Languages

English -IELTS CEFR C1

Arabic -Native

French/Spanish

**Emotion Recognition System Based on Improved Adaboost, Cairo, Egypt** 

OCTOBER 2019 — JUNE 2020

AlphaZero Reimplementation with Reinforcement Learning, Cairo, Egypt

JANUARY 2020 — MAY 2020

OCR for Arabic cursive text, Cairo, Egypt

OCTOBER 2019 — NOVEMBER 2019

Online Courses (deeplearning.ai)

**AI for Medical Diagnosis** 

CREDIENTIAL ID: 55MLGM5SF2AR

**Convolutional Neural Networks** 

CREDIENTIAL ID: 7XCDDJ2XQK9N

Improving Deep Neural Networks: Hyperparameter tuning,

**Regularization and Optimization** 

CREDIENTIAL ID: 5Y3BBEJPP42P

**Neural Networks and Deep Learning** 

CREDIENTIAL ID: KKE4SWKS7GHX

**Structuring Machine Learning Projects** 

CREDIENTIAL ID: 7VSJYDMUAGK8

**Sequences, Time Series and Prediction** 

CREDIENTIAL ID: 9LP5NXG5ZUB6

**Natural Language Processing with Classification and Vector Spaces** 

CREDIENTIAL ID: AL5W42TFV7CM

#### **Extracurricular Activities**

Red bull CYMI Regional Winner (Travelling Competition)

Poverty Alleviation Volunteer

## **Academic Awards**

Erasmus Mundus Masters Full Scholarship

Annual Tuition Scholarships at Cairo University (5 Years).

MOHE Research Funding in JAPAN

Erasmus+ Traineeship Grant

High School Highest Achiever.

## References

<u>Prof. AbdelMoneim Bayoumi</u> <u>Prof. Daniel Neagu</u>